

CONTACT

500 243 437

wojtek_jankowski@o2.pl

O Lublin

Repository

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Codewars

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- · Python junior
- SQL- junior
- Django junior
- HTML junior
- CSS junior
- · JavaScript junior

COMPETENCES

- ability to work independently and in a team - coordination of international projects
- · work with the client
- work with documentation analysis of legal acts
- loyalty I have been working in one company for 12 years

LANGUAGE

• English B2

INTERESTS

- baking cakes
- football
- bicycle touring

WOJCIECH JANKOWSKI

JUNIOR PYTHON DEVELOPER

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Beginner Python programmer who wants to gain new skills and experience in the IT industry. I have analytical skills, and thanks to my previous experience I can work well in a team. I gain my knowledge from online courses, e.g. Udemy, from industry literature, to later verify what I've learned by solving tasks on Codewars.

I am motivated by the possibility of personal development and the challenges I face. I will be happy to join the team, which I will be able to support with my skills and from whom I could learn.

IT PROJECT:

Name: MyLife

A project prepared in the Django framework, where on the example of your virtual CV enriched with a personal blog, relational database connections, a contact form, a login panel are presented, and all this is "dressed" in an aesthetic form.

Technologies: Python, Django, SQL, HTML, CSS

Project repository: Mylife

EDUCATION

Python from scratch

Software Development Academy (291 h)

Python

SQL databases

Software testing

- Algorithms and data structures
- · Frontend technologies
- Backend technologies

Economics

Maria Curie-Skłodowska University 10/2004-08/2010

Business with Financial Services

The University of Huddersfield 09/2007-07/2008

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chief specialist

Lublin City Office

09/2011- present

09/2022-present

- implementation of non-investment projects, including international ones
- · cooperation and maintaining contacts with external entities
- · reporting on performed tasks
- customer service in individual cases in the field of public administration